emirates247.com 2018-06-28

# Privacy Policy - Emirates 24|7

By accessing and using [www.emirates247.com](http://www.emirates247.com/) (‘the Website’) you are agreeing to both the Terms & Conditions and this Privacy & Cookies Policy. You should therefore read both documents before using the Website in full. Emirates247.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. However, it is necessary to collect certain information about our users to ensure that our service is continually improved. We automatically collect some data about our users' browsing actions and patterns. This is aggregate data and does not identify any individual. Other personal information may be collected. This includes information provided voluntarily by users in the course of entering competitions, offers, and registering on the website, among other activities. When you contact us voluntarily – for example, by email – or have any financial dealings with us, or our trading partners -- this also gives us information.

**Use of Information**

Aggregate user information does not identify individuals, and is used to help us improve our understanding of our users and their preferences. It may also be used to assist in auditing use of the website, as well as directing editorial, advertising and commercial opportunities. Information about individual users may be used in several ways – including, but not limited to – the following:

• To contact you about editorial material, commercial offers, and other opportunities that may be of interested to you. - To conduct market research and other surveys.   
• To be shared with advertisers, trading partners and other commercial entities with whom we have or might have an association. We may also be able to share the information that they obtain about their users, which may include you.

**Information Sharing**

We may share your personal information with other group companies, and with third parties whom we have selected carefully and with whom we have, or may have, a commercial relationship. Emirates247.com takes all reasonable care to ensure that your information is secure and private and is only seen by responsible third parties. However, we cannot be held responsible for the actions of any third party who receives or obtains access to the information, or for any breach of security. If you have any concerns about the sharing of your personal details with third parties you can Contact Us at any time to let us know of any objections you may have to how we use or disclose your data in the ways set out in this Privacy Policy. Your personal details may in any event be shared with third party organisations we have contracted to provide services to us, on an agency basis, which include processing data. We may also have to release information (which could include the contents of e-mail communications between any persons) because of a legal requirement on us or pursuant to a court order.

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser of your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. Two types of cookies may be used on the website: - Session Cookies are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the website. These allow you to carry information across pages of the website and avoid having to re-enter information. - Persistent Cookies remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of each specific cookie). Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you, but do help us recognise you as a unique visitor when you return to the website.

**Third Party cookies**

Third parties may serve cookies via the website. These are used for the following purposes: - To serve advertisements on the website and track whether these advertisements are clicked on by users. - To control how often you are shown a particular advertisement. - To count the number of anonymous users of the website. - To provide security within transactions.

**Use of Web Beacons**

Some of our web pages may contain electronic images know as web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign.

**Disabling/Enabling Cookies**

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of the website if cookies are disabled.

**International Transfer of Personal Data**

Services on the net are accessible globally so collection and transmission of personal data is not always confined to one country. You should be aware that by using the website and those of our partners or any site we link through to, your personal data may be processed in or transferred to other countries, and you agree to your personal data being transferred or processed in this way.

**Further Information**

If you wish to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy and your wishes about your personal information, please email us at [editor@emirates247.com](https://mail.dubaiholding.com/OWA/redir.aspx?C=9ed1a2f15fd945f5b1acefcaf0f2cc73&URL=mailto%3aeditor%40emirates247.com).
